newzimbabwe.com 2018-04-02

# Video news and interviews: The latest news, showbiz and sports videos

We, New Zimbabwe Media Ltd; [ www.newzimbabwe.com](http://www.newzimbabwe.com/), (also known as "Newzim", "New Zimbabwe", "New Zimbabwe Group", "NZML" or any other name that maybe used now or in future to refer to the brand) are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information.

Collection Of Information 

In order to provide the services you want, and to allow you to experience a more personalised service when you revisit us, we need to know your interests. We find these out by asking you, by reading your comments and by looking at which are the most popular areas of this Web Site.

Collection Of Personal Information

We will only collect personal information from you (such as name, address, telephone number, email address etc) which you have provided voluntarily to us either by completing registration or enquiry forms or sending emails to us. Please do not submit your personal data to us if you do not wish us to collect it.

Examples of where we may collect and your personal information include (without limitation):

|  (a)  |  information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website (including your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views)   
---|---  
(b)  |  If you order a product or service from us we may ask for information including your name, e-mail address, delivery and billing address. We do not collect or keep any of your financial information. Sometimes we may ask for your telephone number to be forwarded to the couriers who may deliver your order. These details allow us to process your orders efficiently.   
(c)  |  information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us including details   
(d)  |  information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our website services, email notifications and/or newsletters including details   
(e)  |  If you use our "Mail to a friend" service, we ask for the friend's name and email address. We then send an automatic, one-time e-mail inviting your friend to visit us. Details of this transaction are stored only to send that one-time e-mail or to track complaints of mischievous use. Your friend may email management@newzimbabwe.com to ask that it be deleted.   
(f)  |  any other information that you choose to send to us; and other details   
  
Cookies

A cookie consists of information sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser. 

We may use both "session" cookies and “persistent” cookies on the website. We will use the session cookies to: keep track of you whilst you navigate the website; and other uses. We will use the persistent cookies to: enable our website to recognise you when you visit; and other uses. 

Session cookies will be deleted from your computer when you close your browser. Persistent cookies will remain stored on your computer until deleted, or until they reach a specified expiry date.

We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users' computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information. Google's privacy policy is available at: <http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html>.

Our advertisers/payment services providers may also send you cookies.

We publish Google Adsense interest-based advertisements on our website. These are tailored by Google to reflect your interests. To determine your interests, Google will track your behaviour across the web using cookies. You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser using Google's Ads Preference Manager, available at: [ http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/). You can opt-out of the Adsense partner network cookie at: [ http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). However, this opt-out mechanism uses a cookie, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained. To ensure that an opt-out is maintained in respect of a particular browser, you should use the Google browser plug-in available at: <http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/plugin>

Most browsers allow you to reject all cookies, whilst some browsers allow you to reject just third party cookies. For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Internet Options”, “Privacy”, and selecting “Block all cookies” using the sliding selector. Blocking all cookies will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites, including this one.

Using your personal data

Personal data submitted on this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.

We may use your personal information to:

(a)  |  administer the website;   
---|---  
(b)  |  improve your browsing experience by personalising the website;   
(c)  |  enable your use of the services available on the website;   
(d)  |  send to you goods purchased via the website, and supply to you services purchased via the website   
(e)  |  send statements and invoices to you, and collect payments from you;   
(f)  |  send you general (non-marketing) commercial communications;   
(g)  |  send you email notifications which you have specifically requested   
(h)  |  send to you our newsletter and other marketing communications relating to our business or the businesses of carefully-selected third parties which we think may be of interest to you by post or, where you have specifically agreed to this, by email or similar technology you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications   
(i)  |  provide third parties with statistical information about our users – but this information will not be used to identify any individual user;   
(j)  |  deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the website; and   
(k)  |  other uses.   
  
Where you submit personal information for publication on our website, we will publish and otherwise use that information in accordance with the license you grant to us.

We will not without your express consent provide your personal information to any third parties for the purpose of direct marketing.

All our website financial transactions are handled through our payment services provider, Paypal. You should only provide your personal information to Paypal after reviewing the Paypal privacy policy (available at www.paypal.com). We will share information with Paypal only to the extent necessary for the purposes of processing payments you make via our website.

Disclosures

We may disclose information about you to any of our employees, officers, agents, suppliers or subcontractors insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes as set out in this privacy policy.

In addition, we may disclose information about you: 

(a)  |  to the extent that we are required to do so by law;   
---|---  
(b)  |  in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;   
(c)  |  in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk); and   
(d)  |  to the purchaser (or prospective purchaser) of any business or asset which we are (or are contemplating) selling.   
  
Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties.

International Data Transfers

Information that we collect may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which we operate in order to enable us to use the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

Information which you provide may be transferred to countries (including the United States, Japan, other countries)] which do not have data protection laws equivalent to those in force in the European Economic Area.

In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website] will be published on the internet and may be available, via the internet, around the world.

You expressly agree to such transfers of personal information.

Security Of Your Personal Data

We will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

We will store all the personal information you provide on our secure (password- and firewall- protected) servers. All electronic transactions you make to or receive from us will be encrypted using SSL technology including financial ones.

Of course, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet.

You are responsible for keeping your password and user details confidential. We will not ask you for your password.

Policy Amendments

We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes.

We may also notify you of changes to our privacy policy by email.

Your Rights

You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you. Provision of such information may be subject to the payment of a fee (currently fixed at £10.00).

You may instruct us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes by email at any time. (In practice, you will usually either expressly agree in advance to our use of your personal data for marketing purposes, or we will provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of the use of your personal data for marketing purposes.)

Third Party Websites

The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites.

Updating Information

Please let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated. Should your personal information change (e.g. your postcode), or if you no longer wish to receive newsletters or services you have signed up for, or if you wish to review or receive copies of the personal information we hold about you, or have any other queries please email [management@newzimbabwe.com](mailto:management@newzimbabwe.com) including full details of your request.

We may charge a small administration fee in relation to fulfilling a request for access to personal information.

Contact

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal data, please write to us by email to

**New Zimbabwe Media Ltd  
Bromsgrove Business Centre  
57 High Street  
Bromsgrove  
Worcestershire  
B61 8AJ  
**

Data controller

The data controller responsible for our website is New Zimbabwe Media Ltd.

No data transmission over the internet can be entirely secure, and therefore we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information and/or use of our websites. However we use our reasonable endeavours to protect the security of your personal information from unauthorised access or use.

In addition to our safeguards your personal information is protected in the UK by the Data Protection Act 1998. This provides that the information which we hold about you should be processed fairly and lawfully and should be accurate, relevant and not excessive. The information should, where necessary, be kept up to date and not retained for longer than is necessary. Please help us to keep your personal information accurate by updating your registration details on this Web Site.

For more information on the Data Protection Act and the Information Commissioner please see [www.informationcommissioner.gov.uk](http://www.informationcommissioner.gov.uk/)
